hcdistrictclerk.com 2009-05-05

# Office of Harris County District Clerk - Loren Jackson | Privacy Policy

The Harris County District Clerk's Technical Services Bureau maintains the Web site for the Office of the District Clerk of Harris County, Texas as a public service. The following is the privacy policy for this site.

  1. When you log into our Web site, a small cookie will automatically be placed on your PC. The information gathered by the cookie is not reported or used in any manner that would reveal personally identifiable information. Note: A cookie file contains unique information a Web site can use to track such things as password, lists of pages you've visited, and the date when you last looked at a specific page or to identify your session at a particular Web site. A cookie is often used in commercial sites to identify the items selected for a specific shopping cart application.
  2. If you send us an electronic mail message with a question or comment, or fill out a form on our Web site that contains personally identifying information, we will only use the personally identifiable information to respond to your request and analyze trends. We may redirect your message to another government agency or person who is in a better position to answer your question. Your e-mail address shall not be forwarded outside the office of the District Clerk without your consent.
  3. For site management functions, information is collected for analysis and statistical purposes. This information is not reported or used in any manner that would reveal personally identifiable information, and will not be released to any outside parties unless legally required to do so in connection with law enforcement investigations or other legal proceedings. 

We use log analysis tools to create summary statistics, which are used for purposes such as assessing what information is of most interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas. The following information is collected for this analysis:

  * **User Client hostname-** The hostname(or IP address if DNS disabled) of the user/client requesting access.
  * **HTTP header, "user-agent"-** The user-agent information includes the type of browser, its version, and the operating system it's running on.
  * **HTTP header, "refer"-** The referrer specifies the page from which the client accessed the current page.
  * **System date-** The date and time of the user/client request.
  * **Full request-** The exact request the user/client made.
  * **Status-** The status code the server returned to the user/client.
  * **Method-** The request method used.
  * **Universal Resource Identifier(URI)-** The location of a resource on the server.
  * **Query string of the URI-** Anything after the question mark in a URI.
  * **Protocol-** The transport protocol and version used.
